We don't need your maggoty covered.
We're super shy of superstardom. No
glossy photos, no billboard shark.
Sleeping on couches, playing basement.
Free minds won't bow to a corporate art.
They want us clean shaven and posing
pretty. Selling our souls for a 10year
plan, but we'd rather stink of cheap PBR
than sell our songs to a greased up man.
Les our souls for a flashy torn. We'll
leave that ship at the dock. Our velvet
robes and VIP rooms can [\h__\h] right off.
Still not famous, still not sorry. We'd
rather bleed truth than further story.
No way or telling us what to play. We
write our own rules and sing your own
way. Still not famous, still not sorry.
Loud to proud for sorry story. Keep it
in a gar. Drink it till it bleeds.
Freedoms aren't drug just a disease.
They promise exposure a million streams,
but it's just data mine in your teenage
dreams. We're fine with three fans in a
sweaty room. Trading our fame for
creative perfume. No neon signs, no
corporate bailout. We live for the core
changes in our veins. If the scene goes
sideways, we'll still stay true. Cuz the
only thing that's lame for gold bars and
grand illusions. We laugh so hard we
almost pissed. We're allergic to
mentions and rap guitar solos. Give us
real not
sorry. We'd rather play truth than
borrow their story. No, we are telling
us what to play. We write our own rules
and sing our own way. Still not famous,
still not sorry. Loud to pray for your
sorry story. Keep it in a garage. Take
it till it bleeds. Freedoms ar just a
disease.
No leather jackets in boardrooms.
No punched up smiles for campaign pains.
We'll stay broken, loud and restless
while your stars decay and faves chase.
Still not famous. Still not sorry. Still
not famous. Still not sorry. We'd rather
play truth than bother story. No, we
know what to play. We write our own
rules and sing our own right. Still not
famous, still not sorry. Well, through
sorry story
until it bleeds Prince.
Here's to the unsold records and
midnight scars.
[\h__\h] your fame, we'll keep the scars.
Hey. Hey.
Heat. Heat.